– At the left we can see—
but we can see the—
at the right we can see the…
… the head‐snarlers.
And everything is safe… perfectly safe.
Emo?
Emo!
Watch out!
– Ow!
– Are you hurt?
– I don’t think so. You?
– I’m okay.
Get up! Emo, it’s not safe here.
Let’s go.
– What’s next?
– You’ll see!
– You’ll see…
– Emo, this way.
Follow me!
Hurry, Emo!
You’re not paying attention!
– I—I just want
to answer the phone.
– Emo, look— I mean listen.
You have to learn to listen.
This is not some game.
You, I mean we—we could
easily die out here.
Listen.
Listen to the sounds of the machine.
Listen to your breathing.
– Well, don’t you
ever get tired of this?
– Tired?!
– Yeah.
– Emo, the machine
is like clockwork!
One move out of place
and you’re ground to a pulp.
– But isn’t there the… like—
– Pulp, Emo!
Is that what you want? Pulp?
Emo, your goal in life…
… pulp?!
Emo, close your eyes.
– Why?
– Now!
– Okay…
– Good.
What do you see at your left side, Emo?
– Well…
… nothing.
– Really?
– No, nothing at all.
And at your right, what do you
see at your right side, Emo?
– The same, Proog.
Exactly the same, nothing!
– Great.
– Listen, Proog! Do you hear that?
Can we go here?
– There?
– Yeah.
– It isn’t safe, Emo.
– But…
– Trust me, it’s not.
– Or maybe I could—
– No.
– But—
– No! No!
Any further questions, Emo?
– No…
– Emo…
– Yeah?
– Emo, why?
Emo, why can’t you
see the beauty of this place?
The way it works, how perfect it is.
– No, Proog. I don’t see.
I don’t see because
there’s nothing there.
And why should I trust my life
to something that isn’t there?
Well, can you tell me that?
– Emo…
– Answer me.
Proog…
… you’re a sick man!
– Emo…
– Stay away from me!
No! Emo, it’s a trap!
– Hah, “it’s a trap”!
At the left side, you can see
the Hanging Gardens of Babylon!
How’s that for a trap?
– No, Emo!
– And on the right side,
you can see— well guess what…
… the Colossus of Rhodes!
– No!
– The Colossus of Rhodes…
… and it is here just for you, Proog.
“Just for you”.
– It is there.
I’m telling you, Emo.
It—it is. It is.